Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-188
  - Administrative Council June 1989 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Administrative Council May 1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Council background materials April 5, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Council background materials March 1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Council background materials February 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Council background materials January 1989 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Council background materials (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Administrative Council background materials 1988 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Administrative Council background materials 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Administrative Council filing 1988-89 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Deans’ Council / Administrative Council Budget Reposition 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council Future Agendas (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council Future Agendas (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council Archives (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council assorted minutes (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council calendars 1980-89 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council Transitions (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council summer plans (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Council agendas 1981-89 [formerly “in a red binder”] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council loose materials (1) – agenda item materials (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Council loose materials (2) – agenda item materials (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Council loose materials (3) – agenda item materials (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1984 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Council future agendas 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Council assorted records [formerly “in a red binder”] (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Box of audio cassettes from GFG and DPC meetings1990-02 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Box of audio cassettes from Human Resources Council (HRC) and DPC 1989-92 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Box of audio cassettes from DC and Administrative Council (AC) 1989-90 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Box of audio cassettes from University Cabinet (UC) 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bill Weiler, A Compendium of Data and Information about Stanford July 19, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - SU Cabinet Agenda Item materials: University Health and Safety Policies and Impact of New Legislation, March 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Facilities Plan and Funding Forecast 1984-1987 Summary (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SU Annual Financial Report 1984, with annotations to Endowment Investment Summary (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Report of the Task Force on Fraternities and Sororities January 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Regional Planning of the Stanford Campus, September 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Institution Report 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising Policies and Principles 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - DPC [Development Priorities Committee] calendar and members (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PAC-D [Provost’s Advisory Committee-Development] and DPC calendars (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PAC-D charge1992 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PAC-D / DPC reports to Cabinet 1990-92 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Request form: review of (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - GFG / DPC: pending business (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Memo re academic planning and fundraising needs, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - FRAP originals 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising policy memorandum Nov. 25, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Fund request forms (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - GFG/DPG: FRAP mailing (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Request for fundraising form (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Request for fundraising memo 1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Complete Development Priorities Report April 28, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - [untitled: about fundraising approvals] (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Fundraising proposals index (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Good money – bad money 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - PAC-D members 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - GFG/DPC: IBM centennial 1988-89 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate dorm 1986-88 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Endowed Fellows in Residence (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - GFG/DPC: Cross Cultural Program (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - GFG [Green Folders Group] calendar (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Sharon Dickow (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - John Worth (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Jim Rosse (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - DPC/GFG: Jackie’s notes 1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - School reps (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - DPC Reorganization 1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - GFG/DPC logo (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - GFG/DPC: appreciation – J. Barnes (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Featured objectives 1989 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Development organization (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Fundraising policies records 1986-88 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - DPG: H factor (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Research (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Administrative Council Centennial Campaign (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Centennial Campaign clippings (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - SOAC: minutes to ASSU, Acad Secty (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - GFG/DPC: Centennial Campaign literature 1989-91 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Donor recognition (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - GFG/DPC: Faculty Scholars – H Factor (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Residence (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - IBM Centennial Gift SUSE (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Senate: Feb. 9, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - SOAC [Senate Oversight committee on the Centennial Campaign] memberships (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - PAC-D / DPG reports to University Cabinet (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Haresh Shah 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - PAC-D charge (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - PAC-D / DPC calendars, members (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - DPC / PAC-D correspondence 1991 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - GFG/DPC draft minutes 1989 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Featured objective codes 1989 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - [unlabelled – fundraising approvals] (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Fundraising forms – evolving 1992 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - [unlabelled – loose materials] (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - GFG/DPC drafts (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - [unlabelled – loose materials] (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - [unlabelled – loose materials] (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Administrative Council: correspondence, 1983-89 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council: interesting SU memos, 1981-82 and undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council: May 4, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council: May 18, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council: June 1, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council: June 18, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council: June 26, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council: June 29, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Council: July 8, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council: July 23, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Council: July 31, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Council: August 24, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Council: September 8, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Council: September 22, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Council: October 5, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council: October 19, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Council: November 2, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Administrative Council: November 16, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Administrative Council: November 30, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Council: December 4, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Council: December 21, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Administrative Council: January 4, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Administrative Council: January 18, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Administrative Council: February 1, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Administrative Council: February 16, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Administrative Council: March 1, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Administrative Council: March 15, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Administrative Council: April 12, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Administrative Council: April 19, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Council: May 3, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Council: May 11, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Council: May 17, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Administrative Council: May 21, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Administrative Council: May 27, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Administrative Council: June 7, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Council: June 21, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Administrative Council: July 6, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Administrative Council: July 19, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Administrative Council: August 2, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Unfoldered materials described as "Provost’s files." (Box 10)
- Papers, 1989; Accession ARCH-2009-246
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 Aug. 22-31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 Aug. 1-21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 July 20-28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 July 13-18 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 July 11-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 April 26-29 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 April 10-14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 March 16-27 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chron file pertaining to gifts received, 1989 March 6-10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2014-044
  - Inauguration, 1980 Oct 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Inaugural Ball, 1980 Oct 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-014
  - Framed photograph of Donald Kennedy with Stanford University swim team, 1990 (Box 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-168
  - Stanford Centennial, 1991 (Box 1)
  - ANDP Award, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Council of Scientific Society Presidents, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Events at Hoover House, 1990 Aug (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Card, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of State card, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Signed photograph Best Guest Lecturer Award, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cartoon, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gorbachev at Stanford event brochure, 1990 Jun (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fleet Street honorary lifetime member, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cartoon, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - House of Representatives honor, 1997 Jan (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - The Centennial Collection, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Oversize items
    Arrangement
    Oversized materials are stored in map case.
    - Collage, undated; 2017-168_001 (Folder 2017-168_001)
    - Birthday card collage, undated; 2017-168_002 (Folder 2017-168_002)
    - Cartoon, undated; 2017-168_003 (Folder 2017-168_003)
    - Cartoon, undated; 2017-168_004 (Folder 2017-168_004)
    - Stanford Gothic cartoon, undated; 2017-168_005 (Folder 2017-168_005)